Guide to the Laura (Riding) Jackson and Schuyler B. Jackson collection, 1924-1991
Jackson, Laura (Riding) and Schuyler B., 1924-1991
- Series III. Correspondence
  - A) Laura (Riding) Jackson
    - Incoming
      - Essays in Criticism: A Quarterly Journal of Literary Criticism, Apr. 18, 1975 (Box 18, Folder 7)
      - Europa Publications, June 10, 1980 (Box 18, Folder 7)
      - Ewing, Marilyn McKee, Sept. 29, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 7)
      - Faas, Ekbert, May 10, 1979 (Box 18, Folder 7)
      - Faber and Faber, Feb. 3, 1969-Mar. 24, 1987 (Box 19, Folder 1)
      - Facts on File, July 17, 1986 (Box 19, Folder 2)
      - Fain, Grace, Mar. 20, 1972-Feb. 13, 1983 (Box 19, Folder 2)
      - Farmer, Penelope, Oct. 18-Nov. 5, 1983 (Box 19, Folder 2)
      - Farrar, Straus & Giroux, Dec. 21, 1978-Sept. 11, 1987 (Box 19, Folder 2)
      - Fassett Recording Studio, June 26-Sept. 1, 1971 (Box 19, Folder 2)
      - Fawsitt, Honor, Nov. 9, 1988-Feb. 9, 1990 (Box 19, Folder 2)
      - Fendley, Luther, Sept. 10, 1968 (Box 19, Folder 2)
      - Ferry, Bettina, n.d. (Box 19, Folder 2)
      - Field, Edward, June 17, 1977-Oct. 23, 1977? (Box 19, Folder 2)
      - Fincher, Evelyn Davis, Feb. 28, 1974-June 24, 1983, See also: Cornell University Press (Box 19, Folder 2)
      - Fitzgerald, Robert, Feb. 6, 1971-Sept. 12, 1977 (Box 19, Folder 2)
      - Florida Home Finders (Realtor), Jan. 13, 1979 (Box 19, Folder 3)
      - Florida, State of (Box 19, Folder 3)
        - Board of Health, Apr. 3, 1968-Mar. 7, 1969 (Box 19, Folder 3)
        - Department of Agriculture, Feb. 29, 1969-Aug. 22, 1972 (Box 19, Folder 3)
        - Department of Health and Rehabilitative Services (Division of Family Services. Food Stamp Program) (Box 19, Folder 3)
        - Road Department (Florida East Coast Railway Company), Aug. 18, 1972 (Box 19, Folder 3)
        - Treasurer's Office, Dec. 8, 1961-July 7, 1966 (Box 19, Folder 3)
      - Florida, University of, Sept. 8, 1970-Aug. 12, 1976 (Box 19, Folder 3)
        - English Department, Nov. 23, 1970-Nov. 23, 1977 (Box 19, Folder 3)
        - University Libraries, Oct. 28, 1970-Aug. 9, 1974, See also: Monti, Laura, and Gillespie, Jonathan (Box 19, Folder 3)
        - University of Florida Libraries [cont.], Jan. 16, 1975-Jan. 10, 1984 (Box 19, Folder 4)
      - Ford, Hugh, July 14, 1969-Apr. 8, 1972 (Box 19, Folder 5)
      - Ford, Hugh [cont.], Apr. 15, 1972-Sept. 22, 1974 (Box 19, Folder 6)
      - Foulke, Bertha, Apr. 20, 1982 (Box 19, Folder 7)
      - Francis, John W. N., Feb. 19, 1981 (Box 19, Folder 7)
      - Fraser, George S., Aug. 3, 1971-Mar. 5, 1977 (Box 19, Folder 7)
      - Fraser, Paddy, Mar. 2, 1974-May 8, 1984 (Box 20, Folder 1)
      - Freeman, Paul, Jan. 13, 1985 (Box 20, Folder 1)
      - Frey, Lou, Dec. 2, 1969-June 22, 1972 (Box 20, Folder 1)
      - Friedberg, Grace, See: Series III. Correspondence C) Formerly Restricted Correspondence, Grace Friedberg (Box 20, Folder 1)
      - Friedmann, Elizabeth, See: Series III. Correspondence C) Formerly Restricted Correspondence, Elizabeth Friedmann (Box 20, Folder 1)
      - Fruit Shipping Company [with explanatory note by L(R)J], 1947 (Box 20, Folder 2)
      - Fruit Shipping Company [cont.], 1948 (Box 20, Folder 3)
      - Fruit Shipping Company [cont.], 1949 (Box 20, Folder 4)
      - Fruit Shipping Company [cont.], mostly 1950 (Box 20, Folder 5)
      - Fruit Shipping Company [related to the Jacksons' retirement from the business], 1950 (Box 20, Folder 6)
      - Gach, Gary G., 1974-1976 (Box 21, Folder 1)
      - Gale Research Company, July 1, 1987-Feb. 25, 1988 (Box 21, Folder 1)
      - Garland Publishing, June 23, 1980 (Box 21, Folder 1)
      - Gaylord, Jean, Feb. 15, 1977-Mar. 13, 1980, See also: Malloy, Agnes (Box 21, Folder 1)
        - Gaylord, Jean [cont.], May 30, 1980-July 16, 1982 (Box 21, Folder 2)
        - Gaylord, Jean [cont.], July 21, 1982-May 6, 1983 (Box 21, Folder 3)
        - Gaylord, Jean [cont.], May 31, 1983-Apr. 9, 1984 (Box 21, Folder 4)
        - Gaylord, Jean [cont.], Apr. 14, 1984-Dec. 1985 (Box 21, Folder 5)
      - Geiss, John and Wanda, ca. Aug. 11, 1983 (Box 22, Folder 1)
      - George Mason University, Oct. 5, 1973 (Box 22, Folder 1)
      - George Rainbird Ltd., Sept. 25, 1962-Mar. 11, 1963 (Box 22, Folder 1)
      - Gessler, Mrs., Jan. 1977 (Box 22, Folder 1)
      - Ghigna, Charles, Jan. 28, 1974 (Box 22, Folder 1)
      - Giannini, David, Dec. 5, 1968-May 29, 1972 (Box 22, Folder 1)
      - Gilbert, Sandra M., and Gubar, Susan, July 28, 1984 (Box 22, Folder 1)
      - Gillespie, Jonathan, Nov. 23, 1975-Feb. 2, 1977, See also: Florida, University of, University Libraries and Monti, Laura (Box 22, Folder 1)
      - Glackin, Sean, June 15, 1982 (Box 22, Folder 1)
      - Glasgow, University of. Students' Representative Council, ca. 1988 (Box 22, Folder 1)
      - David R. Godine, Publisher, Apr. 27, 1979-July 23, 1979 (Box 22, Folder 1)
      - Goetz, Elise and Warren, Mar. 13, 1979 (Box 22, Folder 1)
      - Gonin, Michael, Feb. 5, 1986 (Box 22, Folder 1)
      - Goodman, Ira J., July 22, 1987 (Box 22, Folder 1)
      - Goodrich, Leslie and Evelyn, ca. Aug. 1983 (Box 22, Folder 1)
      - Gossette, Lucye, Mar. 31, 1968-Feb. 6, 1972 (Box 22, Folder 1)
      - Grad, Wendy, Mar 13, 1978-ca. 1986 (Box 22, Folder 2)
      - Graetz, Claudia Windish, ca. Mar. 1984 (Box 22, Folder 2)
      - Graham, Bob, Apr. 23, 1987 (Box 22, Folder 2)
      - Graham, Gail, Feb. 1982-Feb. 1983 (Box 22, Folder 2)
      - Grand Street, Dec. 2, 1981-Apr. 12, 1982 (Box 22, Folder 2)
      - Granger, John, Aug. 25-Sept. 8, 1987 (Box 22, Folder 2)
      - Graves, Beryl, Mar 12, 1974-July 7, 1977 (Box 22, Folder 2)
      - Graves, Richard Perceval, Sept. 22, 1983-Mar. 12, 1987 (Box 22, Folder 2)
      - Graves, Sally, See: Chilver, Sally See: Series III. Correspondence C) Formerly Restricted Correspondence, E.M. (Sally) Chilver (Box 22, Folder 2)
      - Graves, Tomas, May 5, 1987 (Box 22, Folder 2)
      - Green, Norva, July 10, 1974-Aug. 4, 1975 (Box 22, Folder 2)
      - Greenwood Press, July 28, 1975 (Box 22, Folder 2)
      - Grenfell Press, June 30-July 18, 1986 (Box 22, Folder 2)
      - Guerrard, Philip, Jan. 21, 1975-May 4, 1976 (Box 22, Folder 3)
      - Guest, Barbara, Feb. 5, 1964-Feb. 12, 1984 (Box 22, Folder 3)
      - Guggenheim Foundation, Dec. 1, 1971-Dec. 24, 1975, See: Series III. Correspondence C) Formerly Restricted Correspondence, John Guggenheim Memorial Foundation/James Mathias See also: Mathias, James, and Gaylord, Jean (Box 22, Folder 3)
      - Gurney, Edward J., Sept. 8, 1967-Sept. 1972 (Box 22, Folder 3)
      - Gyldendal Publishers, Jan. 21, 1980 (Box 22, Folder 3)
      - Gyles, Stephen, Aug. 14, 1986 (Box 22, Folder 3)
      - Haberman, Daniel, Mar. 6, 1982 (Box 22, Folder 3)
      - G. K. Hall & Co., See: Hoffman, Michael J. (Box 22, Folder 3)
      - Halpern, Daniel, May 7, 1984, See also: Antaeus (Box 22, Folder 3)
      - Hamburger, Michael, Aug. 24, 1970-Mar. 22, 1971, See also: ["I did not write again to Mr. Hamburger..."] in Series IV. Literary Manuscripts. Unpublished works. Short Essays and Notes (Box 22, Folder 3)
      - Harcourt, Brace & World, July 29, 1970 (Box 22, Folder 3)
      - Harcourt Brace Jovanovich, May 15, 1979 (Box 22, Folder 3)
      - Hargraves, Michael, May 10, 1989 (Box 22, Folder 3)
      - Harmon, Gary L., Mar. 14-June 3, 1977 (Box 22, Folder 3)
      - Harmon, William, See: Series III. Correspondence C) Formerly Restricted Correspondence, William Harmon (Box 22, Folder 4)
      - Harper, Bobby, Apr. 17, 1977-July 31, 1979 (Box 22, Folder 4)
      - Harper, George M[ills], Oct. 30, 1974-Dec. 3, 1979 (Box 22, Folder 4)
      - Harper & Row., See also: McCullough, Frances, May 8, 1972-June 20, 1975 (Box 22, Folder 5)
      - Harvard College. Lamont Library, Oct. 16, 1972-July 20, 1976 (Box 22, Folder 6)
      - Harvard University. Houghton Library, Aug. 1, 1973-Apr. 26, 1974 (Box 22, Folder 6)
      - Harvard University Press, Dec. 23, 1983 (Box 22, Folder 6)
      - Harvey, George, Sept. 6, 1973 (Box 22, Folder 6)
      - Haskell House Publishers, Aug. 14-Sept. 30, 1970 (Box 22, Folder 6)
      - Hasluck, Mary, Apr. 2, 1962 (Box 22, Folder 6)
      - Frank Hedge Public Relations, Mar. 27, 1973 (Box 22, Folder 6)
      - Heft, Marc W., Mar. 25-May 20, 1987 (Box 22, Folder 6)
      - Heinemann, William, May 5, 1970 (Box 22, Folder 6)
      - Henizer, Susan, June 5, 1969-Dec. 1975 (Box 22, Folder 6)
      - Hennefrund, Elizabeth, Apr. 5, 1976-May 7, 1976 (Box 22, Folder 6)
      - Herder and Herder, Feb. 26, 1971-Apr. 13, 1971 [Laura (Riding) Jackson's responses are attached] (Box 22, Folder 6)
      - Hermes, Frances and Jack, July 30, 1968-Dec. 3, 1975 (Box 22, Folder 6)
      - Herschberger, Ruth, Oct. 15, 1969 (Box 22, Folder 6)
      - Hershey, Betty, June 3, 1968-July 12, 1986 (Box 22, Folder 7)
      - Hill, Geoffrey, Oct. 26, 1983 (Box 22, Folder 7)
      - Hill and Wang, See: Farrar, Straus & Giroux See also: Carcanet Press (Box 22, Folder 7)
      - Hirsch, Goldie, Jan. 31, 1973-Jan. 16, 1974 (Box 22, Folder 7)
      - Hirsch, Lucille Frenza, June 9, 1985 (Box 22, Folder 7)
      - Hirsch, Nathaniel, May 17, 1974-Feb. 22, 1980 (Box 22, Folder 7)
      - Hoffman, Jay K., June 27, 1972-Sept. 20, 1972 (Box 23, Folder 1)
      - Hoffman, Michael J., Oct. 5, 1984-May 22, 1986 (Box 23, Folder 1)
      - Hogarth Press, June 18-Nov. 8, 1974 (Box 23, Folder 1)
      - Hollander, Gad, Sept. 21-Dec. 10, 1980 (Box 23, Folder 1)
      - Royal Holloway and Bedford New College, Dec. 30, 1985 (Box 23, Folder 1)
      - Holt, Rinehart and Winston, May 3, 1965-Dec. 1, 1982 (Box 23, Folder 1)
      - Hooshmand, H., Aug. 15, 1984 (Box 23, Folder 1)
      - Horner, Alice, Dec. 1970-Dec. 1977 (Box 23, Folder 1)
      - Horowitz, Glenn, Apr. 23, 1980 (Box 23, Folder 1)
      - Houghton Mifflin, Apr. 23, 1980 (Box 23, Folder 1)
      - Houle, George, Feb. 22, 1980 (Box 23, Folder 1)
      - The Howe Society, ca. Oct. 11, 1984 (Box 23, Folder 2)
      - The Hudson Group, Jul. 10, 1978-Apr. 23, 1979 (Box 23, Folder 2)
      - Hudson Review, Sept. 19, 1972-June 4, 1979 (Box 23, Folder 2)
      - Huggett, Colin, Dec. 15, 1970-Oct. 20, 1973 (Box 23, Folder 2)
      - Humphrey, Arthur, Mar. 6-June 5, 1973 (Box 23, Folder 2)
      - Hurst, Barbara, Sept. 24, 1980 (Box 23, Folder 2)
      - Hynes, Samuel, Feb. 11-Aug. 4, 1975, See also: Wexler, Joyce (Box 23, Folder 2)
      - Indian River County (Box 23, Folder 2)
        - Indian River County Board of County Commissioners, Apr. 28, 1986-Jan. 6, 1987 (Box 23, Folder 2)
        - Indian River County Chamber of Commerce, Nov. 6-Dec. 4, 1985 (Box 23, Folder 2)
        - Indian River County Library, Jan 29-Oct. 23, 1986 (Box 23, Folder 2)
        - Visiting Nurse Association of Indian River County, ca. 1988 (Box 23, Folder 2)
      - Indiana University. The Lilly Library, July 28, 1980 (Box 23, Folder 2)
      - Indiana University Press, July 8-Sept. 11, 1985 (Box 23, Folder 2)
      - Inge, Thomas M., Sept. 23, 1975-Mar. 1, 1976 (Box 23, Folder 2)
      - International Institute of Arts and Letters, Feb. 22, 1958-June 1, 1970 (Box 23, Folder 2)
      - International Platform Association, n.d. (Box 23, Folder 3)
      - International Poetry Society, June 17, 1977 (Box 23, Folder 3)
      - International Press Clippings Bureau, Jan. 25, 1975-Dec. 8, 1983 (Box 23, Folder 3)
      - Israel, Robert, Apr. 26-Oct. 3, 1984 (Box 23, Folder 3)
      - Jackson, John Brinckerhoff, May 23, 1973-Sept. 10, 1974 (Box 23, Folder 4)
      - Jackson, Katharine Townsend, See: Series III. Correspondence C) Formerly Restricted Correspondence, Katharine Townsend Jackson (Box 23, Folder 4)
      - Jackson, Schuyler B., June 18, 1933 (Box 23, Folder 4)
      - Jacobs, Mark, See: Series III. Correspondence C) Formerly Restricted Correspondence, Mark Jacobs (Box 23, Folder 5)
      - James, Lawrence, Dec. 8, 1987-Jan. 23, 1988 (Box 23, Folder 5)
      - Jessup, Annette, Nov. 1987 (Box 23, Folder 5)
      - Johnson, Peter, July 7-July 26, 1977 (Box 23, Folder 5)
      - Johnson Reprint Corporation, Oct. 24, 1966-Sept. 24, 1973 (Box 23, Folder 5)
      - Johnson, Bud and Lucille, Dec. 1975, Apr. 21, 1979 (Box 23, Folder 5)
      - Jones, Harry and Pauline, Feb. 1985-July 12, 1988 (Box 23, Folder 5)
      - Jones, Marvin E. and Minnie, Aug. 1976; n.d. (Box 23, Folder 5)
      - Jowers, Sidney, Mar. 1, 1981-July 8, 1987 (Box 23, Folder 5)
      - Juscik, Steve, ca. 1988 (Box 23, Folder 5)
      - Kale, Herb and Charlotte, Dec. 31, 1981-Dec. 1987 (Box 23, Folder 6)
      - Kamecke, Mary von, Apr. 20, 1970-Jan. 4, 1974 (Box 23, Folder 6)
      - Kansas, University of, at Lawrence, Oct. 12, 1977-Apr. 27, 1978 (Box 23, Folder 6)
      - Kaplan, Herbert E., Mar. 22-Apr. 29, 1977 (Box 23, Folder 6)
      - Kaufman, Carole, and Jeffrey L[eurs?], Oct.-Dec. 1978 (Box 23, Folder 6)
      - Keith, W.J., Apr. 3, 1978 (Box 23, Folder 6)
      - Kemp, Harry, Aug. 14-Oct. 1970 (Box 23, Folder 6)
      - Kennedy, Ponsonby & Prideaux, Jun. 25-Nov. 9, 1980 (Box 23, Folder 6)
      - Kenny, Maurice, Mar. 8, 1985-July 7, 1988 (Box 23, Folder 6)
      - Kentucky, University of, Libraries, Nov. 30, 1977-Apr. 20, 1978 (Box 23, Folder 6)
      - Khalsa, Sat Siri Kaur, Apr. 13, 1979 (Box 23, Folder 6)
      - Kilpatrick, James J., May 1, 1974 (Box 23, Folder 6)
      - Kincaid, Michael, Mar. 20-Apr. 23, 1988 (Box 23, Folder 6)
      - Kingscote-Billinge, L., Nov. 26, 1960 (Box 23, Folder 6)
      - Kirchen, Sherry, Dec. 1978 (Box 23, Folder 6)
      - Kirkham, Michael
        - Kirkham, Michael, May 13, 1969-Aug. 26, 1970 (Box 23, Folder 7)
        - Kirkham, Michael, Sept. 1970-June 1971 (Box 23, Folder 8)
        - Kirkham, Michael, July 1971-July 28, 1976 (Box 24, Folder 1)
        - Kirkham, Michael, Sept. 1976-Mar. 2, 1979 (Box 24, Folder 2)
      - Kivrakides, Petros, and Grigoriadis, Panayiotis, Nov. 28, 1963-Mar. 15, 1968 (Box 24, Folder 3)
      - Kjorsvik, Bertha, Nov. 26, 1970 (Box 24, Folder 3)
      - Knight, Vlasta, 1969 (Box 24, Folder 3)
      - Alfred A. Knopf, Inc., Sept. 20, 1977-Jan. 11, 1978, See also: Random House (Box 24, Folder 3)
      - Kostelanetz, Richard B., May 20, 1987 (Box 24, Folder 3)
      - Kremer, Arthur, Apr. 13, 1989 (Box 24, Folder 3)
      - Krieger, Janet, Jan 14, 1973-Apr. 5, 1982 (Box 24, Folder 3)
      - Kurtz, Emeric J., Aug. 24, 1976 (Box 24, Folder 3)
      - Lancaster, R. D., July 19, 1982 (Box 24, Folder 3)
      - Lance, Jeanne, May. 16, 1984 (Box 24, Folder 3)
      - Allen Lane (A Division of Penguin Books), July 16, 1973 (Box 24, Folder 3)
      - Langfang, Mary and Roland, Apr. 10-Dec. 1975 (Box 24, Folder 3)
      - Language and Style: An International Journal, Oct. 3, 1981-Jan. 27, 1987 (Box 24, Folder 3)
      - The Lapis Press, Feb. 18-Oct. 15, 1987 (Box 24, Folder 4)
      - Larson, Sven, Feb. 22-Apr. 11, 1974 (Box 24, Folder 4)
      - Latham, Robert A., Jan. 29, 1985 (Box 24, Folder 4)
      - Ledwell, Marguerite [Sister], Oct. 28, 1974, Aug. 5, 1975 (Box 24, Folder 4)
      - University of Leicester (Box 24, Folder 4)
        - Leicester University Arts Festival, Aug. 10, 1966 (Box 24, Folder 4)
        - Leicester University Library, Apr. 5, 1981 (Box 24, Folder 4)
      - Leonard, James, June 23, 1961-Aug. 19, 1971 (Box 24, Folder 4)
      - Leverhulme Trust Fund. Research Awards Advisory Committee, Dec. 19, 1978-Oct. 13, 1981 (Box 24, Folder 4)
      - Lewis, Ryer, June 21, 1971 (Box 24, Folder 4)
      - Library of Congress, Aug. 26, 1981-Aug. 29, 1985 (Box 24, Folder 4)
      - Lind, Liv, Jan. 15, 1983 (Box 24, Folder 4)
      - Little, Brown, & Co., Jan. 9, 1939-Aug. 23, 1972 (Box 24, Folder 5)
      - Living Authors, June 21, 1933-June 9, 1934 (Box 24, Folder 6)
      - Locke, Edward, May 29-June 8, 1989 (Box 24, Folder 6)
      - Dr. Jan van Loewen. International Copyright Agency, June 2, 1959-Mar. 8, 1961 (Box 24, Folder 6)
      - London Magazine, n.d. (Box 24, Folder 6)
      - London Review Of Books Aug. 12, 1983 (Box 24, Folder 6)
      - Lord John Press, See: Yellin, Herb (Box 24, Folder 6)
      - Los Angeles, County of. Office of the Public Guardian, Aug. 25-Oct. 6, 1967 (Box 24, Folder 6)
      - Loveland, Jo Lee, Jan. 19, 1983 (Box 24, Folder 6)
      - Lynam, Emma, May 4, 1965-1971 (Box 24, Folder 6)
      - Macdonald, Donald C., Sept. 28, 1959 (Box 24, Folder 7)
      - MacLean, Edith and son, Dec. 1975-Dec. 1978 (Box 24, Folder 7)
      - Macmillan Information, Mar. 9, 1973 (Box 24, Folder 7)
      - Macmillan Accounts and Administration, 1989 (Box 24, Folder 7)
      - Makowsky, Varonica A., July 10-July 17, 1984 (Box 24, Folder 7)
      - Malloy, Agnes, Aug. 21, 1985, See also: Gaylord, Jean (Box 24, Folder 7)
      - Manhattan Theatre Club, Sept. 16, 1982-June 16, 1983 (Box 24, Folder 7)
      - Mariah, Paul, Jan. 29, 1986-Feb. 8, 1988 (Box 24, Folder 7)
      - Mark Twain Journal, Oct. 2, 1986 (Box 24, Folder 7)
      - Marsha, Tony, Sept. 23-Oct. 26, 1987 (Box 24, Folder 7)
      - Mason, Ellsworth (Box 24, Folder 8)
      - Massachusetts Review, Feb. 1, 1971-Mar. 24, 1983 (Box 25, Folder 1)
      - Mathias, Barbara, Jan. 1, 1979-Mar. 12, 1983 (Box 25, Folder 1)
      - Mathias, James, See: Guggenheim Foundation Series III. Correspondence C)Formerly Restricted Correspondence, John Guggenheim Memorial Foundation/James Mathias (Box 25, Folder 1)
      - Mathias, Wilson Stafford, and Lynne, Apr. 10, 1980 (Box 25, Folder 1)
      - Matthews, Thomas S., July 6-Aug. 9, 1968 (Box 25, Folder 1)
      - May, Mary Bailey, Feb. 6, 1985 (Box 25, Folder 1)
      - Mayer, Bernadette, Aug. 1, 1981-Jan. 27, 1986 (Box 25, Folder 2)
      - Mayers family [Arthur, David, Lena, Margaret, Sophie], Aug. 29, 1967-Feb. 20, 1979 (Box 25, Folder 3)
      - Mayers, Richard, See: Series III. Correspondence C) Formerly Restricted Correspondence, Richard Mayers (Box 25, Folder 3)
      - McCagg, Katherine Jackson, See: Series III. Correspondence C) Formerly Restricted Correspondence, Katherine McCagg (Box 25, Folder 3)
      - McCallie, Margaret, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 4)
      - McCormick, Bradford, Apr. 22-May 4, 1981 (Box 25, Folder 4)
      - McCullough, Frances, Feb. 13, 1976-Feb. 23, 1977, See also: Dial Press, Harper & Row (Box 25, Folder 4)
      - McElrath, Joe, Jan. 23, 1980 (Box 25, Folder 4)
      - McEwen, Mary, May 1977 (Box 25, Folder 4)
      - McGraw-Hill Company, Dec. 9, 1964-Feb. 2, 1973 (Box 25, Folder 4)
      - McInerney, Brian, Aug. 10, 1984-Dec. 11, 1987, See also: New York Public Library (Box 25, Folder 5)
      - McIntosh and Otis, Inc., June 5, 1969 (Box 25, Folder 6)
      - McKinley, James, Sept. 13, 1972-Jan. 30, 1974 (Box 25, Folder 6)
      - McKinney, Erma Jean, Feb. 25-July 9, 1969 (Box 25, Folder 6)
      - McManus, Michael, Aug. 5, 1977 (Box 25, Folder 6)
      - G. & C. Merriam Company, Sept. 28, 1962-Dec. 23, 1976 (Box 25, Folder 6)
      - Meserole, Harrison T., Apr. 17-Apr. 26, 1977 (Box 25, Folder 6)
      - Meyers, Jeffrey, Feb. 14-Feb. 28, 1978 (Box 25, Folder 6)
      - Meyers, John Bernard, Aug. 27, 1982 (Box 25, Folder 6)
      - Miami Herald, May 18, 1972 (Box 25, Folder 6)
      - Michigan State University, June 27, 1974-Oct. 21, 1975 (Box 25, Folder 6)
      - Miller, Leslie [Lila] and Donald, Dec. 1971-May 8, 1981 (Box 25, Folder 6)
      - Miller, Harold, Mar. 14, 1978 (Box 25, Folder 6)
      - Miller, Nella [Byrdie], Apr. 14, 1971-Dec. 1972 (Box 25, Folder 6)
      - Miller, Stephen Paul, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 6)
      - Miller, Ted and Anne [Carrie], 1976? (Box 25, Folder 6)
      - The Minnesota Review, Feb. 14,-Apr. 10, 1967 (Box 25, Folder 7)
      - Modern Language Quarterly, Oct. 1, 1971-Mar. 28, 1975 (Box 25, Folder 7)
      - Mohr, Charles and Dorothy, Dec. 1975-Dec. 1977 (Box 25, Folder 7)
      - Montemarano, Dan, Dec. 3, 1981 (Box 25, Folder 7)
      - Monti, Laura, Dec. 1971-Apr. 5, 1979, See also: Florida University Libraries (Box 25, Folder 7)
      - Moody, Gil, Oct. 1986 (Box 25, Folder 7)
      - Morgan, Bill, Jan. 1, 1985 (Box 25, Folder 7)
      - Morgan, Edwin, Dec. 1978-1989 (Box 25, Folder 7)
      - Morris, Susan, Dec. 1974-Sept. 1, 1984, See also: Carcanet Press, and Florida, State of, Treasurer's Office (Box 25, Folder 7)
      - Morrow, Bradford, Mar. 11, 1980, See also: Conjunctions, Mosaic, Journal of Comparative Study of International Literature, Art and Ideas. (Box 25, Folder 8)
      - Mount Holyoke College, Willistone Memorial Library, Nov. 1974-Aug. 7, 1977 (Box 25, Folder 8)
      - Muller, Adolf, Feb. 23, 1983 (Box 25, Folder 8)
      - Mycue, Edward, Mar. 10, 1980 (Box 25, Folder 8)
      - Narkiewicz, Mary, Oct. 1, 1980-July 20, 1987 (Box 25, Folder 8)
      - Nashville, Tennessee. Joint University Libraries, Jan. 16, 1984-Nov. 23, 1974, See also: Vanderbilt University Library (Box 25, Folder 8)
      - The Nation, Apr. 4, 1979 (Box 25, Folder 8)
      - National Audubon Society, Mar. 13, 1975, See also: Pelican Island Audubon Society (Box 25, Folder 8)
      - National Book League, Dec. 15, 1953-Jan. 28, 1954 (Box 25, Folder 8)
      - National Endowment for the Arts, Apr. 22, 1980-Mar. 30, 1981 (Box 25, Folder 8)
      - National Republican Congressional Committee, Nov. 18, 1966 (Box 25, Folder 8)
      - National Review, Apr. 28-June?, 1983 (Box 25, Folder 8)
      - Nebel, Margie, Dec. 20, 1968-Dec. 1970 (Box 25, Folder 8)
      - Neely, Montrose and Carl, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 8)
      - Nettman, David, Nov. 20, 1982 (Box 25, Folder 8)
      - New American Library, Nov. 10, 1976 (Box 25, Folder 8)
      - Newman, John, May 6, 1969 (Box 25, Folder 8)
      - Newman, Paul and Elsie, 1969 (Box 25, Folder 8)
      - Newman, Ruth, Oct. 5, 1965-June 22, 1968 (Box 25, Folder 8)
      - New Mexico, State of, State Planning Office, Mar. 25-July 16, 1969 (Box 25, Folder 8)
      - Newspool, June 3, 1984 (Box 26, Folder 1)
      - The New Yorker, Nov. 24, 1976 (Box 26, Folder 1)
      - New York Public Library, Dec. 23, 1974-July 7, 1980, See also: McInerney, Brian and Szladits, Lola (Box 26, Folder 1)
      - The New York Review of Books, Aug. 8, 1972-June 24, 1987 (Box 26, Folder 1)
      - The New York Times, July 2, 1969-Dec. 16, 1970 (Box 26, Folder 1)
      - The New York Times Book Review, July 14, 1969-Sept. 18, 1970 (Box 26, Folder 1)
      - Nickles, Mamie, Apr. 21, 1964-Dec. 1977 (Box 26, Folder 1)
      - Nolan, John, See: Series III. Correspondence C) Formerly Restricted Correspondence, John Nolan (Box 26, Folder 1)
      - David C. Nolte, Sept. 18, 1986 (Box 26, Folder 1)
      - North Point Press, May 9, 1980-Apr. 22, 1988 (Box 26, Folder 2)
      - Northwestern University. University Library. Special Collections Department, July 21, 1970-June 20, 1979 (Box 26, Folder 2)
      - W. W. Norton & Company, Jan. 4, 1972-Sept. 17, 1973 (Box 26, Folder 2)
      - W. W. Norton & Company, Sept. 21, 1973-Mar. 18, 1985 (Box 26, Folder 3)
      - Nye, Robert, See: Series III. Correspondence C) Formerly Restricted Correspondence, Robert and Judith Nye See also: Seymour-Smith, Martin (Box 26, Folder 4)
      - Harold Ober Associates, Oct. 16, 1969 (Box 26, Folder 4)
      - O'Brien, Pat, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 4)
      - The Observer, Oct. 2, 1970-Nov. 13, 1970 (Box 26, Folder 4)
      - Occasional Papers, Nov. 18, 1971-Feb. 16, 1972 (Box 26, Folder 4)
      - Occident (Associated Students, University of California), Feb. 15-Mar. 1954 (Box 26, Folder 4)
      - O'Clair, Hanna, Apr. 22, 1973 (Box 26, Folder 4)
      - O'Clair, Midge, Sept. 12, 1972-Mar. 30, 1973 (Box 26, Folder 4)
      - O'Clair, Robert, June 30, 1972-June 12, 1974 (Box 26, Folder 4)
      - Ofri-Scheps, Dorith, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 4)
      - O'Gorman, Ted, May 29, 1979-Mar. 1980 (Box 26, Folder 4)